<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<documents>
  <document>
    <docID>se5</docID>
    <docDate></docDate>
    <docSource></docSource>
    <docText>Report Date 27 April, 2003. Intercept of cell phone 804-774-8920. In a very brief call from this number to phone number 703-659-2317 on 26 April, 2003, the caller speaks in Arabic. A translation reads: "We are now prepared to take the crescent to victory".</docText>
    <Date>27 April, 2003</Date>
    <Phone>703-659-2317</Phone>
    <Phone>804-774-8920</Phone>
    <Date>26 April, 2003</Date>
    <Misc>Arabic</Misc>
  </document>
  <document>
    <docID>se4</docID>
    <docDate></docDate>
    <docSource></docSource>
    <docText>Report Date 24 April, 2003. Phone calls on 22 April, 2003 from 703-659-2317 to the following numbers: 804-759-6302; 804-774-8920; 718-352-8479; and 01 1207670734. The same brief voice message was given in Arabic in each call. A translation of this message reads: "I will be in my office on April 30 at 9:OOAM. Try to be on time".</docText>
    <Phone>804-759-6302</Phone>
    <Date>22 April, 2003</Date>
    <Date>24 April, 2003</Date>
    <Phone>703-659-2317</Phone>
    <Phone>804-774-8920</Phone>
    <Misc>Arabic</Misc>
    <Phone>718-352-8479</Phone>
    <Phone>01 1207670734</Phone>
    <Date>April 30</Date>
  </document>
  <document>
    <docID>se3</docID>
    <docDate></docDate>
    <docSource></docSource>
    <docText>Report Date 21 April, 2003: Frequent recent phone calls from 703-659-2317 to the following numbers: 804-759-6302 [Richmond, VA., listed in the name Clark Webster]; 804-774-8920 [Charlottesville, VA, listed in the name Mukhtar Galab]; 718-352-8479 [Queens, NYC, listed in the name Bagwant Dhaliwal. Two overseas calls were made to 01 1207670734 [Amsterdam, The Netherlands, listed in the name Hans Pakes].</docText>
    <Person>Hans Pakes</Person>
    <Location>The Netherlands</Location>
    <Person>Bagwant Dhaliwal</Person>
    <Phone>804-759-6302</Phone>
    <Person>Clark Webster</Person>
    <Location>Richmond</Location>
    <Location>Virginia</Location>
    <Location>Amsterdam</Location>
    <Phone>703-659-2317</Phone>
    <Location>Queens</Location>
    <Location>New York City</Location>
    <Person>Mukhtar Galab</Person>
    <Location>Charlottesville</Location>
    <Phone>804-774-8920</Phone>
    <Phone>718-352-8479</Phone>
    <Phone>01 1207670734</Phone>
    <Date>21 April, 2003</Date>
  </document>
  <document>
    <docID>se2</docID>
    <docDate></docDate>
    <docSource></docSource>
    <docText>Report Date 20 April, 2003: lntercept of phone calls made from 718-352-8479 at 2462 Myrtle Ave. Apt. 307, Queens. NYC revealed several calls to a phone 732-455-6392 in North Bergen, New Jersey. listed in the name of Hani al Hallak, who manages a carpet store. In the latest call, the caller from 2462 Myrtle Ave. Apt. 307, Queens, NYC announced that he would pick up the carpet he ordered on April 25, 2003.</docText>
    <Date>20 April, 2003</Date>
    <Location>Queens</Location>
    <Location>New York City</Location>
    <Location>Myrtle Ave</Location>
    <Location>North Bergen</Location>
    <Person>Hani al Hallak</Person>
    <Phone>718-352-8479</Phone>
    <Phone>732-455-6392</Phone>
    <Date>April 25, 2003</Date>
  </document>
  <document>
    <docID>se1</docID>
    <docDate></docDate>
    <docSource></docSource>
    <docText>Report Date 10 April, 2003. lntercept of a mobile phone message on 6 April, 2003 from 706-437-6673 to 713-556-9213. The first number was traced to a resident of Columbus, Georgia whose address is: 2237 St. Mary's Road. The resident at this address, Ralph Goode, claims that his mobile phone was recently stolen from his car, a matter he says he reported on 30 March, 2003 to the Columbus police. The Columbus police verified this account. The second number was traced to 2339 Little York Rd., Apt 7 in Houston, Texas. The caller from 706-437-6673, speaking in Arabic, said [when translated]: "What you need will be found in the usual place". The second number was listed by Sprint PCS as belonging to a Jamal Kalifa.</docText>
    <Date>30 March, 2003</Date>
    <Organization>Sprint</Organization>
    <Location>Georgia</Location>
    <Date>10 April, 2003</Date>
    <Date>6 April, 2003</Date>
    <Location>Texas</Location>
    <Location>Houston</Location>
    <Person>Jamal Kalifa</Person>
    <Misc>Arabic</Misc>
    <Location>Columbus</Location>
    <Person>Ralph Goode</Person>
    <Location>Little York Rd.</Location>
    <Phone>706-437-6673</Phone>
    <Phone>713-556-9213</Phone>
    <Location>St. Mary's Road</Location>
  </document>
  <document>
    <docID>fbi9</docID>
    <docDate></docDate>
    <docSource></docSource>
    <docText>Report Date 16 April, 2003. FBI Special Report: In Seattle, Washington on 15 April, 2003 a US Post Office on Howell St. reported that six identical packages, each marked "Home Made Candies", were sent to state government officials in Seattle. Each one had the return address: 1635 Alder St, Seattle, Washington. A check by an alert postal employee revealed that there is no such address in Seattle. This employee also stated that she believed the sender was a Middle Eastern man who paid in cash for the postage. The packages were given to the Seattle police who treated them as if they might be package bombs, which indeed they were. They were set off in a vacant field managed by the police for such purposes.</docText>
    <Organization>FBI</Organization>
    <Date>16 April, 2003</Date>
    <Misc>Middle Eastern</Misc>
    <Date>15 April, 2003</Date>
    <Location>Washington</Location>
    <Organization>US Post Office</Organization>
    <Location>Seattle</Location>
    <Location>Howell St.</Location>
    <Location>Alder St</Location>
  </document>
  <document>
    <docID>fbi8</docID>
    <docDate></docDate>
    <docSource></docSource>
    <docText>Report Date 15 April, 2003. FBI from INS: Two men were arrested on 14 April, 2003 at Bush Intercontinental Airport in Houston, Texas. They are identified as Jamal Kalifa and Abul Hassan Salman. They both attempted to purchase airline tickets using Dutch passports that are believed to have been forged in Paris, France. The tickets they attempted to purchase were on Continental Airlines flight #458 from Bush Intercontinental in Houston to Reagan National Airport in Washington, DC.</docText>
    <Location>Paris</Location>
    <Organization>INS</Organization>
    <Date>14 April, 2003</Date>
    <Misc>Dutch</Misc>
    <Organization>FBI</Organization>
    <Location>Texas</Location>
    <Location>Houston</Location>
    <Date>15 April, 2003</Date>
    <Person>Jamal Kalifa</Person>
    <Location>Washington</Location>
    <Organization>Bush Intercontinental Airport</Organization>
    <Person>Abul Hassan Salman</Person>
    <Location>France</Location>
    <Organization>Continental Airlines</Organization>
    <Organization>Reagan National Airport</Organization>
  </document>
  <document>
    <docID>fbi7</docID>
    <docDate></docDate>
    <docSource></docSource>
    <docText>Report Date 15 April, 2003. FBI: The Powhatan Company is a manufacturer of military explosives of various types, including C-4. It is located just outside of Keswick. Virginia. On 11 April, 2003 this company reported that 200 pounds of C-4 could not be accounted for during a recent inventory.</docText>
    <Location>Virginia</Location>
    <Organization>FBI</Organization>
    <Location>Keswick</Location>
    <Misc>C-4</Misc>
    <Date>15 April, 2003</Date>
    <Date>11 April, 2003</Date>
    <Organization>The Powhatan Company</Organization>
  </document>
  <document>
    <docID>fbi6</docID>
    <docDate></docDate>
    <docSource></docSource>
    <docText>Report Date 15 April, 2003. FBI Special report: Dr. Clark Adams, a Middle Eastern expert whose office is at the Pentagon, was last seen on 13 April, 2003 after he left his home at 1830hrs for the Home Depot store on Lee Highway in Merrifield, VA. Dr. Adams's family could give no explanation for his disappearance. The FBI is treating his disappearance as a possible case of abduction.</docText>
    <Location>Virginia</Location>
    <Organization>FBI</Organization>
    <Date>13 April, 2003</Date>
    <Misc>Middle Eastern</Misc>
    <Date>15 April, 2003</Date>
    <Person>Clark Adams</Person>
    <Organization>Pentagon</Organization>
    <Organization>Home Depot</Organization>
    <Location>Lee Highway</Location>
    <Location>Merrifield</Location>
  </document>
  <document>
    <docID>fbi5</docID>
    <docDate></docDate>
    <docSource></docSource>
    <docText>Report Date 13 April, 2003. FBI from Border Patrol in El Paso, Texas: Border patrol agents in Hudspeth County, Texas reported that on the night of 10 April, 2003, they apprehended two men, whom they first believed to be Mexicans, crossing the Rio Grande river near McNary, Texas. As they were being interrogated at the McNary police station, it was discovered that each man carried $20,000 in cash. The two men, when interrogated, spoke no Spanish but had Texas drivers' licenses made out in the names Vincent Cortez and Arnaldo Gueterrez. The address given on both licenses was: 1212 McRae Blvd, El Paso, Texas. They also had one-way tickets on an American Airlines flight from El Paso to Houston. Texas, scheduled to leave El Paso on 16 April, 2003. An investigation made of the residence at 1212 McRae Blvd. in El Paso revealed that it was occupied by two men named Ben Hassine and Ahmed Yassin, both of whom claim to be students at the University of Texas at El Paso.</docText>
    <Organization>American Airlines</Organization>
    <Organization>FBI</Organization>
    <Date>16 April, 2003</Date>
    <Date>10 April, 2003</Date>
    <Date>13 April, 2003</Date>
    <Location>Texas</Location>
    <Location>Houston</Location>
    <Organization>Border Patrol</Organization>
    <Location>El Paso</Location>
    <Location>Hudspeth County</Location>
    <Misc>Mexicans</Misc>
    <Location>Rio Grande</Location>
    <Location>McNary</Location>
    <Misc>Spanish</Misc>
    <Person>Vincent Cortez</Person>
    <Person>Arnaldo Gueterrez</Person>
    <Person>Ben Hassine</Person>
    <Person>Ahmed Yassin</Person>
    <Organization>University of Texas</Organization>
    <Location>McRae Blvd</Location>
    <Money>$20,000</Money>
  </document>
  <document>
    <docID>fbi4</docID>
    <docDate></docDate>
    <docSource></docSource>
    <docText>Report Date 13 April, 2003. FBI from Army CID: A man who gave his name as Wallace Wilson was arrested at 1730hrs on 10 April, 2003 at Camp George West Military Reservation in Denver, Colorado. Wilson was able to obtain access to this military reservation using personal identification in the form of a Colorado driver's license and a Social Security card. He also used identification for the truck he was driving that is owned by his employer, the Apex Paper Products Company in Denver, Colorado. This company has a contract to supply paper products to Camp George West. A man by the name Wallace Wilson is known to be a member of a domestic militia group known as Aryan Nations. Wilson was arrested by MPs when he was seen loading boxes on his Apex truck. The boxes were being taken from an apparently unlocked storage facility at Camp George West. The boxes contained 50 Cat ammunition and several land mines</docText>
    <Location>Denver</Location>
    <Location>Colorado</Location>
    <Organization>FBI</Organization>
    <Location>Camp George West Military Reservation</Location>
    <Date>10 April, 2003</Date>
    <Date>13 April, 2003</Date>
    <Person>Wallace Wilson</Person>
    <Misc>Social Security</Misc>
    <Organization>Apex Paper Products Company</Organization>
    <Organization>Aryan Nations</Organization>
    <Organization>Army CID</Organization>
  </document>
  <document>
    <docID>fbi3</docID>
    <docDate></docDate>
    <docSource></docSource>
    <docText>Report Date: 8 April, 2003. FBI: On 7 April, 2003 at 0600 hrs. Police began tailing a panel truck rented from Ryder Truck Rental in Culver City, California. According to Ryder, this truck was rented on 1 April, 2C03 by a man who gave the name Karm Bensaid. Bensaid showed a California drivers' license and gave his home address as 452 Hubbard St. in Culver City. Bensaid told the Rvder sales aren't that he would need a small truck for two days to move some item: of furniture from Culver City to San Gabriel, California. When the buck was still not returned on 6 April, the Ryder agent notified Los Angeles police who, in turn, notified the FBI. On 6 April, 2003 an alert LA police officer noticed the truck parked in front of an apartment complex on Greenlawn Ave. in Culver City. On 7 April, two men were observed to enter this rental truck. They drove south on US 405 and exited right at Imperial Highway. They then turned left on Sheldon St. and stopped at the City Park in El Segundo, California. At this point the two men were apprehended by police and FBI agents. In the truck were found two pairs of binoculars, maps of the Los Angeles area, and flight schedules to and from LAX.</docText>
    <Location>US</Location>
    <Organization>FBI</Organization>
    <Location>Los Angeles</Location>
    <Date>6 April, 2003</Date>
    <Organization>Ryder Truck Rental</Organization>
    <Location>Culver City</Location>
    <Location>California</Location>
    <Person>Karm Bensaid</Person>
    <Location>San Gabriel</Location>
    <Location>Greenlawn Ave.</Location>
    <Location>Imperial Highway</Location>
    <Location>City Park</Location>
    <Location>El Segundo</Location>
    <Location>LAX</Location>
    <Date>8 April, 2003</Date>
    <Date>7 April, 2003</Date>
    <Location>Sheldon St.</Location>
    <Location>Hubbard St.</Location>
  </document>
  <document>
    <docID>fbi25</docID>
    <docDate></docDate>
    <docSource></docSource>
    <docText>Report Date 27 April, 2003. FBI [From police in North Bergen, NJ]: In the early morning hours of April 26, 2003 a passerby reported a fire in a carpet shop that is managed by a Hani al Hallak of North Bergen . The fire seems to have been started the night before when someone tossed a cigarette butt into a waste basket in the basement of the shop. While firemen were extinguishing the blaze, they discovered several cartons labeled: PRIVATE: DO NOT OPEN. These cartons contained C-4 explosive. Attempts to reach Hani ai Hallak have not been successful. An employee at the carpet shop later told police that al Hallak had just gone on a vacation in Canada and that he had left no address.</docText>
    <Date>27 April, 2003</Date>
    <Location>New Jersey</Location>
    <Organization>FBI</Organization>
    <Location>North Bergen</Location>
    <Person>Hani al Hallak</Person>
    <Location>Canada</Location>
    <Misc>C-4</Misc>
    <Date>April 26, 2003</Date>
  </document>
  <document>
    <docID>fbi24</docID>
    <docDate></docDate>
    <docSource></docSource>
    <docText>Report Date 27 April, 2003. FBI: In an examination of storage unit #I74 at the Budget Storage Units in Keswick, VA, fifty pounds of C-4 plastic explosive were found along with some fusing devices.</docText>
    <Date>27 April, 2003</Date>
    <Location>Virginia</Location>
    <Organization>FBI</Organization>
    <Location>Keswick</Location>
    <Organization>Budget Storage Units</Organization>
    <Misc>C-4</Misc>
  </document>
  <document>
    <docID>fbi23</docID>
    <docDate></docDate>
    <docSource></docSource>
    <docText>Report Date 27 April, 2003. FBI: A man named Carl Louis, whose residence is at 3410 Van Dyke Avenue in Detroit Michigan, was arrested by Detroit police for helping foreigners obtain Michigan drivers' licenses using forged documents. Carl Louis is specifically charged with providing forged documents for a Lebanese national named Abdelhak Kherbane, who was arrested in connection with the attempted bombing on 2 April of the Beth Israel synagogue in Detroit, Michigan.</docText>
    <Date>27 April, 2003</Date>
    <Organization>FBI</Organization>
    <Person>Carl Louis</Person>
    <Location>Detroit</Location>
    <Location>Michigan</Location>
    <Misc>Lebanese</Misc>
    <Person>Abdelhak Kherbane</Person>
    <Organization>Beth Israel</Organization>
    <Location>Van Dyke Avenue</Location>
  </document>
  <document>
    <docID>fbi22</docID>
    <docDate></docDate>
    <docSource></docSource>
    <docText>Report Date 27 April, 2003. FBI: A photo of the man using the name Mark Davis was examined by a representative of the Canadian police in NYC. The Canadian police investigator identified the man in the photo to be Hamid Alwan, a Saudi who overstayed a travel visa and is wanted by the police in Canada. It is now known that Alwan received explosives training in the Sudan and in Afghanistan.</docText>
    <Date>27 April, 2003</Date>
    <Location>Afghanistan</Location>
    <Location>Sudan</Location>
    <Misc>Saudi</Misc>
    <Organization>FBI</Organization>
    <Location>New York City</Location>
    <Person>Mark Davis</Person>
    <Location>Canada</Location>
    <Misc>Canadian</Misc>
    <Person>Hamid Alwan</Person>
    <Person>Alwan</Person>
  </document>
  <document>
    <docID>fbi21</docID>
    <docDate></docDate>
    <docSource></docSource>
    <docText>Report Date 26 April, 2003. Coast Guard intelligence to FBI and CIA: A routine reporting of ships bound for the USA. This report contains departure date, place, destination, cargo manifest and crew roster and is required 96 hours before arrival in ports in the USA. Report from Amsterdam on 25 April, 2003 lists one container ship bound for the US, the Holland Queen, which is bound for Boston. Arrival time in Boston of the Holland Queen is 29 April, 1930hrs.</docText>
    <Misc>Holland Queen</Misc>
    <Location>US</Location>
    <Location>Amsterdam</Location>
    <Date>25 April, 2003</Date>
    <Organization>FBI</Organization>
    <Date>26 April, 2003</Date>
    <Organization>Coast Guard</Organization>
    <Location>Boston</Location>
    <Date>29 April, 1930</Date>
    <Date>29 April, 1930hrs</Date>
  </document>
  <document>
    <docID>fbi20</docID>
    <docDate></docDate>
    <docSource></docSource>
    <docText>Report Date 26 April, 2003. FBI: A check of rented storage facilities in the Richmond and Charlottesville areas reveals that a man giving his name as Abdulla Ramzi rented storage unit # 174 on 10 April, 2003 at the Budget Storage Units in Keswick, VA. Ramzi gave his address as 2932 University Drive, Charlottesville, VA. Ramzi paid in cash for a month's rental.</docText>
    <Location>Richmond</Location>
    <Location>Virginia</Location>
    <Organization>FBI</Organization>
    <Location>Charlottesville</Location>
    <Date>26 April, 2003</Date>
    <Date>10 April, 2003</Date>
    <Location>Keswick</Location>
    <Organization>Budget Storage Units</Organization>
    <Person>Abdulla Ramzi</Person>
    <Location>University Drive</Location>
  </document>
  <document>
    <docID>fbi2</docID>
    <docDate></docDate>
    <docSource></docSource>
    <docText>Report Date: 5 April, 2003. FBI: Passport control at Dulles Airport in Washington DC records that Abdul Ramazi, holder of US passport # 177183634 [issued by Passport Agency, Wash. DC on 12 Feb. 19971 has made three trips to Amsterdam, two trips to Hamburg, Germany, and three trips to Cairo, Egypt in the last five months. The address given by Ramazi on his passport is 1176 Floyd Ave., Springfield, VA. Phone number at this address is 703-734-0104.</docText>
    <Location>US</Location>
    <Person>Abdul Ramazi</Person>
    <Location>Virginia</Location>
    <Location>Germany</Location>
    <Location>Hamburg</Location>
    <Location>Amsterdam</Location>
    <Organization>FBI</Organization>
    <Location>Springfield</Location>
    <Location>Egypt</Location>
    <Location>Dulles Airport</Location>
    <Location>Washington DC</Location>
    <Organization>Passport Agency</Organization>
    <Location>Cairo</Location>
    <Phone>703-734-0104</Phone>
    <Date>5 April, 2003</Date>
    <Date>12 Feb. 1997</Date>
    <Location>Wash. DC</Location>
    <Location>Floyd Ave.</Location>
  </document>
  <document>
    <docID>fbi19</docID>
    <docDate></docDate>
    <docSource></docSource>
    <docText>Report Date 25 April, 2003. FBI: A report from AMTRAK reveals a reservation, paid in cash in Charlottesville, and made by Faysal Goba on 23 April, 2003. Reservation is for three one-way first class tickets and one sleeping compartment from Charlottesville, VA to Atlanta, GA on 29 April, 2003. Reservation is on AMTRAK Train # 19, which runs between Penn Station NYC and New Orleans, LA. Reservations are in the names: Faysal Goba, Mukhtar Galab and Yasein Mosed.</docText>
    <Location>Virginia</Location>
    <Person>Faysal Goba</Person>
    <Date>23 April, 2003</Date>
    <Date>25 April, 2003</Date>
    <Organization>FBI</Organization>
    <Person>Mukhtar Galab</Person>
    <Location>Charlottesville</Location>
    <Person>Yasein Mosed</Person>
    <Location>Georgia</Location>
    <Location>Los Angeles</Location>
    <Organization>AMTRAK</Organization>
    <Location>Atlanta</Location>
    <Organization>Penn Station NYC</Organization>
    <Location>New Orleans</Location>
    <Date>29 April, 2003</Date>
  </document>
  <document>
    <docID>fbi18</docID>
    <docDate></docDate>
    <docSource></docSource>
    <docText>Report dated 25 April, 2003. FBI: A U-Haul truck was found abandoned on Colfax Avenue in Denver, Colorado nor far from the Camp George West Military Reservation. The truck had two blown front tires. Examination of the truck's contents revealed 16 land mines. The U-haul rental Agency in Denver was contacted and they reported that this truck had been rented in Denver on 20 April, 2003 by a man who used, as identification, a Colorado driver's license in the name Masood Yaser. The address on this license is: 1660 Coal Mine Road, Apartment 206. The owner of this apartment complex stated on 22 April, 2003 that Masood Yaser had rented Apartment # 206, but had left one week ago and did not leave a forwarding address.</docText>
    <Location>Denver</Location>
    <Location>Colorado</Location>
    <Person>Masood Yaser</Person>
    <Location>Coal Mine Road</Location>
    <Date>20 April, 2003</Date>
    <Date>22 April, 2003</Date>
    <Date>25 April, 2003</Date>
    <Organization>FBI</Organization>
    <Location>Camp George West Military Reservation</Location>
    <Location>Colfax Avenue</Location>
    <Organization>U-haul</Organization>
  </document>
  <document>
    <docID>fbi17</docID>
    <docDate></docDate>
    <docSource></docSource>
    <docText>Report Date 22 April, 2003. FBI: There is no residence with address 1631 Capitol Ave. in Richmond, Virginia. The phone number given for this address [804-759-6302] is in fact a Sprint cell phone registered in the name Faysal Goba.</docText>
    <Phone>804-759-6302</Phone>
    <Location>Richmond</Location>
    <Location>Virginia</Location>
    <Location>Capitol Ave.</Location>
    <Person>Faysal Goba</Person>
    <Date>22 April, 2003</Date>
    <Organization>FBI</Organization>
    <Organization>Sprint</Organization>
  </document>
  <document>
    <docID>fbi16</docID>
    <docDate></docDate>
    <docSource></docSource>
    <docText>Report Date 22 April, 2003. FBI: Hani al Hallak, of North Bergen NJ, has deposited checks in his bank account that were drawn on First Union Bank account number 1070173749003 in Springfield VA in the name Abdul Ramazi. The latest check is dated 16 April, 2003 and was in the amount of $8500.</docText>
    <Person>Abdul Ramazi</Person>
    <Date>22 April, 2003</Date>
    <Location>New Jersey</Location>
    <Organization>FBI</Organization>
    <Misc>1070173749003</Misc>
    <Organization>First Union Bank</Organization>
    <Location>North Bergen</Location>
    <Date>16 April, 2003</Date>
    <Location>Springfield VA</Location>
    <Person>Hani al Hallak</Person>
    <Money>$8500</Money>
  </document>
  <document>
    <docID>fbi15</docID>
    <docDate></docDate>
    <docSource></docSource>
    <docText>Report Date 20 April, 2003: FBI: Mukhtar Galab has an account at the Virginia National Bank in Charlottesville, VA. Bank records say he has deposited several checks in the last three months, totaling $13,000, drawn on account number 1070173749003 held by Abdul Ramazi at the First Union Bank in Springfield, VA.</docText>
    <Person>Abdul Ramazi</Person>
    <Location>Virginia</Location>
    <Date>20 April, 2003</Date>
    <Organization>FBI</Organization>
    <Location>Springfield</Location>
    <Phone>1070173</Phone>
    <Misc>1070173749003</Misc>
    <Person>Mukhtar Galab</Person>
    <Location>Charlottesville</Location>
    <Organization>First Union Bank</Organization>
    <Organization>Virginia National Bank</Organization>
    <Money>$13,000</Money>
  </document>
  <document>
    <docID>fbi14</docID>
    <docDate></docDate>
    <docSource></docSource>
    <docText>Report Date 20 April, 2003. FBI: Security officers at O'Hare airport in Chicago, Illinois arrested two American Airlines baggage handlers named Omar Clark and Joseph Nizar. They were observed opening luggage that was about to be transferred from a United Connector flight from Green Bay, Wisconsin to a United flight into New York City. Their backgrounds are now being investigated by the FBI.</docText>
    <Organization>American Airlines</Organization>
    <Date>20 April, 2003</Date>
    <Organization>FBI</Organization>
    <Location>New York City</Location>
    <Location>O'Hare</Location>
    <Location>Chicago</Location>
    <Location>Illinois</Location>
    <Person>Omar Clark</Person>
    <Person>Joseph Nizar</Person>
    <Organization>United Connector</Organization>
    <Location>Green Bay</Location>
    <Location>Wisconsin</Location>
    <Organization>United</Organization>
  </document>
  <document>
    <docID>fbi13</docID>
    <docDate></docDate>
    <docSource></docSource>
    <docText>Report Date 20 April, 2003. FBI: Also listing 2462 Myrtle Ave. Apt. 307, Queens, NYC as his home address is Bagwant Dhaliwal, who is also employed by Empire State Vending Services in Manhattan.</docText>
    <Person>Bagwant Dhaliwal</Person>
    <Date>20 April, 2003</Date>
    <Organization>FBI</Organization>
    <Location>Queens</Location>
    <Location>New York City</Location>
    <Location>Myrtle Ave</Location>
    <Organization>Empire State Vending Services</Organization>
    <Location>Manhattan</Location>
  </document>
  <document>
    <docID>fbi12</docID>
    <docDate></docDate>
    <docSource></docSource>
    <docText>Report Date 19 April, 2003. FBI: In an interview with Shiela Watson, she said she simply made a mistake in listing her home address on her NYSE vendors' ID application. She had recently moved and gave her earlier address by mistake.</docText>
    <Organization>FBI</Organization>
    <Organization>New York Stock Exchange</Organization>
    <Person>Shiela Watson</Person>
    <Date>19 April, 2003</Date>
  </document>
  <document>
    <docID>fbi11</docID>
    <docDate></docDate>
    <docSource></docSource>
    <docText>Report Date 18 April, 2003. FBI: An INS check of expired student visas reveals the names Mukhtar Galab and Yasein Mosed. They have been enrolled at the University of Virginia in Charlottesville, Virginia. Checks with the University of Virginia reveal that these two persons have not attended any classes for the past two semesters. The address they both gave to the University of Virginia is 2932 University Drive, Charlottesville, VA. There is presently no one living at this address. A check with mobile phone providers shows that a Sprint cell phone # 804-774-8920 is registered in the name Mukhtar Galab.</docText>
    <Location>Virginia</Location>
    <Organization>INS</Organization>
    <Organization>FBI</Organization>
    <Person>Mukhtar Galab</Person>
    <Location>Charlottesville</Location>
    <Organization>Sprint</Organization>
    <Person>Yasein Mosed</Person>
    <Organization>University of Virginia</Organization>
    <Phone>804-774-8920</Phone>
    <Date>18 April, 2003</Date>
    <Location>2932 University Drive</Location>
  </document>
  <document>
    <docID>fbi10</docID>
    <docDate></docDate>
    <docSource></docSource>
    <docText>Report Date April 18, 2003. FBI: A routine check of security at the New York Stock Exchange lNYSEl reveals some anomalies in background checks of several persons who now hold vendor's IDS that allow them access to the NYSE provided that they are accompanied by security guards. (i) A man named Steven Clark, employed by the City Computer Services Corp. failed, in his application for a NYSE vendor's ID, to report his arrest and conviction [I2 December, 20011 on a charge of assault and battery. He served six months in jail and is now out on probation. (ii) Shiela Watson, employed by the Clark &amp; Co. Office Supplies Co., gave her current home address on her application for a vendor's ID as: 1631 Webster Ave.. The Bronx. NYC. There is no one by the name Shiela Watson at this residence. (iii) A man named Mark Davis, reported age 32 years, obtained a social security card and a New York State Driver's license in 1999 using a birth certificate now believed to have been forged. He is employed by Empire State Vending Services in Manhattan and he services vending machines such as coffee, soft drink, and candy machines. He lists his home address as: 2462 Myrtle Ave. Apt. 307, Queens, NYC.</docText>
    <Organization>FBI</Organization>
    <Location>Queens</Location>
    <Location>New York City</Location>
    <Location>Myrtle Ave</Location>
    <Person>Mark Davis</Person>
    <Organization>Empire State Vending Services</Organization>
    <Location>Manhattan</Location>
    <Organization>New York Stock Exchange</Organization>
    <Person>Shiela Watson</Person>
    <Person>Steven Clark</Person>
    <Organization>City Computer Services Corp.</Organization>
    <Organization>Clark &amp; Co</Organization>
    <Organization>Office Supplies Co.</Organization>
    <Location>Webster Ave.</Location>
    <Location>Bronx</Location>
    <Date>April 18, 2003</Date>
    <Date>2 December, 2001</Date>
    <Location>New York</Location>
    <Date>I2 December, 20011</Date>
  </document>
  <document>
    <docID>fbi1</docID>
    <docDate></docDate>
    <docSource></docSource>
    <docText>Report Date: 1 April, 2003. FBI: Abdul Ramazi is the owner of the Select Gourmet Foods shop in Springfield Mall, Springfield, VA. [Phone number 703-659-2317]. First Union National Bank lists Select Gourmet Foods as holding account number 1070173749003. Six checks totaling $35,000 have been deposited in this account in the past four months and are recorded as having been drawn on accounts at the Pyramid Bank of Cairo, Egypt and the Central Bank of Dubai, United Arab Emirates. Both of these banks have just been listed as possible conduits in money laundering schemes.</docText>
    <Date>1 April, 2003</Date>
    <Person>Abdul Ramazi</Person>
    <Location>Virginia</Location>
    <Location>United Arab Emirates</Location>
    <Phone>703-659-2317</Phone>
    <Organization>FBI</Organization>
    <Location>Springfield</Location>
    <Location>Egypt</Location>
    <Phone>1070173</Phone>
    <Misc>1070173749003</Misc>
    <Organization>Select Gourmet Foods</Organization>
    <Location>Springfield Mall</Location>
    <Organization>First Union National Bank</Organization>
    <Organization>Pyramid Bank of Cairo</Organization>
    <Organization>Central Bank of Dubai</Organization>
    <Money>$35,000</Money>
  </document>
  <document>
    <docID>cia9</docID>
    <docDate></docDate>
    <docSource></docSource>
    <docText>Report date 25 April, 2003. CIA [From Dutch security]: Analysis of radioactive particles found in truck driven by Tawfiq al Adel and Saeed Khallad, and in the storage unit rented by Saleh al Ahdal and Riduan bin Attash, reveals them to be powdered cesium 137. One ounce of this substance could spread radioactive fallout over 60 city blocks.</docText>
    <Organization>CIA</Organization>
    <Misc>Dutch</Misc>
    <Person>Tawfiq al Adel</Person>
    <Person>Saeed Khallad</Person>
    <Date>25 April, 2003</Date>
    <Person>Riduan bin Attash</Person>
    <Person>Saleh al Ahdal</Person>
    <Misc>cesium 137</Misc>
  </document>
  <document>
    <docID>cia8</docID>
    <docDate></docDate>
    <docSource></docSource>
    <docText>Report Date 24 April, 2003. CIA [From Dutch Security]: An address in Haarlem was found in the truck driven by Tawfiq al Adel and Saeed Khallad. This address is for an apartment rented in Haarlem by, two Saudi's who hold Dutch passports. Jelte Nijboer [the apartment owner] says they also rent storage unit # 206. The two men al Ahdal and bin Attash are employed as container loaders at Sealink Container Corp. in Amsterdam. This corporation owns a large fleet of containers that are shipped all over the world and subsequently hauled on trains or trucks. Inspection of unit # 206 on 23 April, 2003 reveals radiation traces, one pair of lead gloves, and two sticks of TNT. Also found are pieces of a wooden crate. Pieces of this crate, also revealing radioactive traces, are labeled and identify a company in Lublin, Poland.</docText>
    <Organization>CIA</Organization>
    <Misc>Dutch</Misc>
    <Location>Haarlem</Location>
    <Date>24 April, 2003</Date>
    <Location>Amsterdam</Location>
    <Misc>Saudi</Misc>
    <Date>23 April, 2003</Date>
    <Person>Saeed Khallad</Person>
    <Person>Jelte Nijboer</Person>
    <Person>al Ahdal</Person>
    <Organization>Sealink Container Corp.</Organization>
    <Location>Lublin</Location>
    <Location>Poland</Location>
    <Person>Tawfiq al Adel</Person>
    <Person>bin Attash</Person>
  </document>
  <document>
    <docID>cia7</docID>
    <docDate></docDate>
    <docSource></docSource>
    <docText>Report Date 22 April, 2003. CIA [From Dutch Security]: Two men were arrested on April 20, 2003 by Dutch police in Haarlem, The Netherlands after leaving the scene of an accident in which they were involved. Later on April 21, 2003 these men were identified as Tawfiq al Adel and Saeed Khaliad who have been wanted in Hamburg. Germany in connection with investigations of Al Qaeda operations in Europe. They were driving a panel truck rented in Hamburg, Germany. Radioactive traces were found in bed of this truck.</docText>
    <Organization>CIA</Organization>
    <Location>The Netherlands</Location>
    <Organization>Al Qaeda</Organization>
    <Date>22 April, 2003</Date>
    <Location>Germany</Location>
    <Location>Hamburg</Location>
    <Misc>Dutch</Misc>
    <Person>Tawfiq al Adel</Person>
    <Location>Haarlem</Location>
    <Person>Saeed Khaliad</Person>
    <Location>Europe</Location>
    <Date>April 20, 2003</Date>
    <Date>April 21, 2003</Date>
  </document>
  <document>
    <docID>cia6</docID>
    <docDate></docDate>
    <docSource></docSource>
    <docText>Report Date 22 April, 2003: CIA From German Intelligence: On 20 April, 2003, German intelligence reported that a container chosen at random for inspection at the docks in Bremerhaven, Germany contained a crate in which there were four Stinger missiles. The box was addressed to Marvel Corporation, 1632 Trenton Avenue, Trenton, New Jersey, USA. The shipper's address was given as: 16 Rhinelander Platz., Hamburg, Germany. German intelligence advises that there is no such address in Hamburg. The serial numbers on the four Stinger missiles identifies them as being from among the nearly 400 Stinger missiles, now missing, which were given in the late 1980s to Taliban fighters in Afghanistan.</docText>
    <Organization>CIA</Organization>
    <Location>Afghanistan</Location>
    <Location>US</Location>
    <Organization>Taliban</Organization>
    <Date>20 April, 2003</Date>
    <Date>22 April, 2003</Date>
    <Location>New Jersey</Location>
    <Location>Germany</Location>
    <Location>Hamburg</Location>
    <Location>Bremerhaven</Location>
    <Misc>Stinger</Misc>
    <Organization>Marvel Corporation</Organization>
    <Location>Trenton Avenue</Location>
    <Location>Trenton</Location>
    <Organization>German Intelligence</Organization>
    <Location>Rhinelander Platz.</Location>
  </document>
  <document>
    <docID>cia5</docID>
    <docDate></docDate>
    <docSource></docSource>
    <docText>Report Date 20 April, 2003. CIA: On 19 April, a car bomb was set off near the American Diplomatic Mission Headquarters in Buenos Aires. There were no casualties since the bomb seems to have gone off prematurely. The driver of the car carrying the bomb Survived. He has been identified as Jamil Musawi, who is known to be a member of Hezboliah. This organization has had a presence in several Latin American countries.</docText>
    <Date>20 April, 2003</Date>
    <Organization>American Diplomatic Mission Headquarters</Organization>
    <Location>Buenos Aires</Location>
    <Person>Jamil Musawi</Person>
    <Location>Hezboliah</Location>
    <Misc>Latin American</Misc>
  </document>
  <document>
    <docID>cia4</docID>
    <docDate></docDate>
    <docSource></docSource>
    <docText>Report Date 14 April, 2003. CIA: From an interrogation of a cooperative detainee in Guantanamo. Detainee says he trained daily with a man named Ziad al Shibh at an Al Qaeda explosives training facility in the Sudan in 1994. From a captured laptop computer in Afghanistan it is learned that Ziad al Shibh holds a United Arab Emirates passport in the name Faysal Goba. INS check reveals that a Faysal Goba, from the United Arab Emirates, entered the USA on a travel visa in January of 2003 stating that he would be visiting a person named Clark Webster in Richmond, Va. The contact address given by Goba was: 1631 Capitol Ave., Richmond VA; phone number: 804-759-6302.</docText>
    <Organization>CIA</Organization>
    <Location>Afghanistan</Location>
    <Organization>Al Qaeda</Organization>
    <Location>US</Location>
    <Location>Guantanamo</Location>
    <Phone>804-759-6302</Phone>
    <Person>Clark Webster</Person>
    <Location>Richmond</Location>
    <Location>Virginia</Location>
    <Organization>INS</Organization>
    <Date>14 April, 2003</Date>
    <Location>Sudan</Location>
    <Location>Capitol Ave.</Location>
    <Person>Faysal Goba</Person>
    <Location>United Arab Emirates</Location>
    <Person>Ziad al Shibh</Person>
    <Date>1994</Date>
  </document>
  <document>
    <docID>cia3</docID>
    <docDate></docDate>
    <docSource></docSource>
    <docText>Report Date 12 April, 2003. CIA From French Intelligence: Acting on a tip from an unnamed source, French police arrested an Egyptian named Muhammad Shamzi at his home at 16 Rue St. Sebastien in Paris on 8 April, 2002. In his home police found 200 US and 180 British blank passports. In addition, on the hard drive of Shamzi's laptop computer was a record of a US and British passports that Shamzi had apparently forged. One of these passports was made out in the name Masood Yaser, whose address was listed as 1660 Coal Mine Road, Apartment 206, Denver, Colorado, USA. Another US passport forged was in the name Vincent Lozario, 2229 Marshall Avenue. Minneapolis, Minnesota, USA. A third forged US passport was in the name Khalfan Maulid, 656 Laurel Avenue, Bowling Green, Kentucky, USA.</docText>
    <Location>Paris</Location>
    <Location>US</Location>
    <Location>Denver</Location>
    <Location>Colorado</Location>
    <Person>Masood Yaser</Person>
    <Location>Coal Mine Road</Location>
    <Misc>CIA</Misc>
    <Misc>French</Misc>
    <Misc>Egyptian</Misc>
    <Person>Muhammad Shamzi</Person>
    <Misc>British</Misc>
    <Person>Vincent Lozario</Person>
    <Location>Marshall Avenue</Location>
    <Location>Minneapolis</Location>
    <Location>Minnesota</Location>
    <Person>Khalfan Maulid</Person>
    <Location>Laurel Avenue</Location>
    <Location>Bowling Green</Location>
    <Location>Kentucky</Location>
    <Date>12 April, 2003</Date>
    <Date>8 April, 2002</Date>
    <Location>Rue St. Sebastien</Location>
  </document>
  <document>
    <docID>cia2</docID>
    <docDate></docDate>
    <docSource></docSource>
    <docText>Report Date: 9 April, 2003. CIA [From a detainee at Guantanamo, Cuba who has given the name Abdul al Hada]: During an interview with CIA officers in March of 2003, al Hada is reported to have said: "In April 2003 there is not such good weather for flying". Asked what he meant by this statement, the detainee said: "That's for you to figure out". The detainee would not elaborate further.</docText>
    <Organization>CIA</Organization>
    <Person>Abu al Masri</Person>
    <Location>Guantanamo</Location>
    <Location>Cuba</Location>
    <Person>Abdul al Hada</Person>
    <Date>9 April, 2003</Date>
    <Date>April 2003</Date>
    <Date>March of 2003</Date>
  </document>
  <document>
    <docID>cia11</docID>
    <docDate></docDate>
    <docSource></docSource>
    <docText>Report Date 27 April, 2003. CIA: From a laptop computer captured in Afghanistan it was learned that a Pakistani named Sahim Albakri, who fought with the Taliban in 1990 - 1992, travels using an Indian passport in the name Bagwant Dhaliwal. On this same computer was found the name Muhammed bin Harazi, who served with the Taliban from 1987 - 1993. Records on this computer reveal that Muhammed bin Harazi entered the USA in March, 1993 and uses the alias Abdul Ramazi.</docText>
    <Organization>CIA</Organization>
    <Date>27 April, 2003</Date>
    <Location>Afghanistan</Location>
    <Person>Bagwant Dhaliwal</Person>
    <Location>US</Location>
    <Person>Abdul Ramazi</Person>
    <Organization>Taliban</Organization>
    <Misc>Pakistani</Misc>
    <Person>Sahim Albakri</Person>
    <Misc>Indian</Misc>
    <Person>Muhammed bin Harazi</Person>
    <Date>March, 1993</Date>
    <Date>1990 - 1992</Date>
    <Date>1987 - 1993</Date>
  </document>
  <document>
    <docID>cia10</docID>
    <docDate></docDate>
    <docSource></docSource>
    <docText>Report Date 27 April, 2003. CIA: The Holland Queen crew roster lists a person named Hans Pakes as being aboard the Holland Queen. Pakes works in the ship's galley. From an Al Qaeda laptop computer captured in Afghanistan there is a roster of trainees In an explosives training unit in Kandahar, 1996. Abu al Masri, a Yemeni is listed on this roster. The record says he left for The Netherlands in January 1996. He is using the alias: Hans Pakes.</docText>
    <Organization>CIA</Organization>
    <Date>27 April, 2003</Date>
    <Person>Hans Pakes</Person>
    <Location>The Netherlands</Location>
    <Location>Afghanistan</Location>
    <Misc>Holland Queen</Misc>
    <Organization>Al Qaeda</Organization>
    <Location>Kandahar</Location>
    <Misc>Yemeni</Misc>
    <Person>Abu al Masri</Person>
    <Date>January 1996</Date>
    <Date>1996</Date>
  </document>
  <document>
    <docID>cia1</docID>
    <docDate></docDate>
    <docSource></docSource>
    <docText>Report Date: 1 April, 2003. CIA [From ME]: On 30 March, 2003 the British Special Branch arrested Omar Bakri Qatada at his home at #11 St. Mary's Terrace, Paddington, London. Found in Qatada's bedroom was a small carton holding 10 ounces of Pentaerythritol [PETN] and Triacetone Triperoxide [TATP]. This is the same explosive that Richard Reid attempted to use on American Airlines #63 from Paris to Miami on 22 December, 2001. The BSB were alerted to follow and detain Qatada on the basis of information obtained from a respected moderate Moslem cleric in London, whose name was not provided in this report from M15.</docText>
    <Date>30 March, 2003</Date>
    <Location>Paris</Location>
    <Organization>American Airlines</Organization>
    <Date>1 April, 2003</Date>
    <Organization>CIA</Organization>
    <Organization>British Special Branch</Organization>
    <Person>Omar Bakri Qatada</Person>
    <Location>St. Mary 's Terrace</Location>
    <Location>Paddington</Location>
    <Location>London</Location>
    <Person>Qatada</Person>
    <Person>Richard Reid</Person>
    <Location>Miami</Location>
    <Misc>Moslem</Misc>
    <Date>22 December, 2001</Date>
    <Misc>Pentaerythritol</Misc>
    <Misc>Triacetone Triperoxide</Misc>
    <Organization>M15</Organization>
  </document>
  <aliases>
    <alias>
      <alias_primary_id>
        <Location>Georgia</Location>
      </alias_primary_id>
      <alias_other_id>
        <Location>GA</Location>
      </alias_other_id>
    </alias>
    <alias>
      <alias_primary_id>
        <Location>Los Angeles</Location>
      </alias_primary_id>
      <alias_other_id>
        <Location>LA</Location>
      </alias_other_id>
    </alias>
    <alias>
      <alias_primary_id>
        <Location>New Jersey</Location>
      </alias_primary_id>
      <alias_other_id>
        <Location>NJ</Location>
      </alias_other_id>
    </alias>
    <alias>
      <alias_primary_id>
        <Location>New York City</Location>
      </alias_primary_id>
      <alias_other_id>
        <Location>NYC</Location>
      </alias_other_id>
    </alias>
    <alias>
      <alias_primary_id>
        <Location>Richmond</Location>
      </alias_primary_id>
      <alias_other_id>
        <Location>Richmond VA</Location>
      </alias_other_id>
    </alias>
    <alias>
      <alias_primary_id>
        <Location>US</Location>
      </alias_primary_id>
      <alias_other_id>
        <Location>USA</Location>
      </alias_other_id>
    </alias>
    <alias>
      <alias_primary_id>
        <Location>Virginia</Location>
      </alias_primary_id>
      <alias_other_id>
        <Location>VA</Location>
      </alias_other_id>
      <alias_other_id>
        <Location>Va</Location>
      </alias_other_id>
      <alias_other_id>
        <Location>VA.</Location>
      </alias_other_id>
    </alias>
    <alias>
      <alias_primary_id>
        <Organization>British Special Branch</Organization>
      </alias_primary_id>
      <alias_other_id>
        <Organization>BSB</Organization>
      </alias_other_id>
    </alias>
    <alias>
      <alias_primary_id>
        <Organization>Bush Intercontinental Airport</Organization>
      </alias_primary_id>
      <alias_other_id>
        <Organization>Bush Intercontinental</Organization>
      </alias_other_id>
    </alias>
    <alias>
      <alias_primary_id>
        <Person>Faysal Goba</Person>
      </alias_primary_id>
      <alias_other_id>
        <Person>Goba</Person>
      </alias_other_id>
    </alias>
    <alias>
      <alias_primary_id>
        <Organization>New York Stock Exchange</Organization>
      </alias_primary_id>
      <alias_other_id>
        <Organization>NYSE</Organization>
      </alias_other_id>
    </alias>
    <alias>
      <alias_primary_id>
        <Organization>Apex Paper Products Company</Organization>
      </alias_primary_id>
      <alias_other_id>
        <Organization>Apex</Organization>
      </alias_other_id>
    </alias>
    <alias>
      <alias_primary_id>
        <Organization>Ryder Truck Rental</Organization>
      </alias_primary_id>
      <alias_other_id>
        <Organization>Ryder</Organization>
      </alias_other_id>
    </alias>
    <alias>
      <alias_primary_id>
        <Organization>Sprint</Organization>
      </alias_primary_id>
      <alias_other_id>
        <Organization>Sprint PCS</Organization>
      </alias_other_id>
    </alias>
    <alias>
      <alias_primary_id>
        <Person>Abdul Ramazi</Person>
      </alias_primary_id>
      <alias_other_id>
        <Person>Ramazi</Person>
      </alias_other_id>
    </alias>
    <alias>
      <alias_primary_id>
        <Location>Camp George West Military Reservation</Location>
      </alias_primary_id>
      <alias_other_id>
        <Location>Camp George West</Location>
      </alias_other_id>
    </alias>
    <alias>
      <alias_primary_id>
        <Person>Hans Pakes</Person>
      </alias_primary_id>
      <alias_other_id>
        <Person>Pakes</Person>
      </alias_other_id>
    </alias>
    <alias>
      <alias_primary_id>
        <Person>Abu al Masri</Person>
      </alias_primary_id>
      <alias_other_id>
        <Person>al Hada</Person>
      </alias_other_id>
    </alias>
    <alias>
      <alias_primary_id>
        <Person>Hani al Hallak</Person>
      </alias_primary_id>
      <alias_other_id>
        <Person>al Hallak</Person>
      </alias_other_id>
    </alias>
    <alias>
      <alias_primary_id>
        <Person>Karm Bensaid</Person>
      </alias_primary_id>
      <alias_other_id>
        <Person>Bensaid</Person>
      </alias_other_id>
    </alias>
    <alias>
      <alias_primary_id>
        <Person>Clark Adams</Person>
      </alias_primary_id>
      <alias_other_id>
        <Person>Adams</Person>
      </alias_other_id>
    </alias>
    <alias>
      <alias_primary_id>
        <Person>Muhammad Shamzi</Person>
      </alias_primary_id>
      <alias_other_id>
        <Person>Shamzi</Person>
      </alias_other_id>
    </alias>
    <alias>
      <alias_primary_id>
        <Person>Abdulla Ramzi</Person>
      </alias_primary_id>
      <alias_other_id>
        <Person>Ramzi</Person>
      </alias_other_id>
    </alias>
    <alias>
      <alias_primary_id>
        <Person>Wallace Wilson</Person>
      </alias_primary_id>
      <alias_other_id>
        <Person>Wilson</Person>
      </alias_other_id>
    </alias>
  </aliases>
</documents>